justfly.com 2018-12-06

# Privacy Policy - JustFly

We at JustFly take your privacy very seriously. Maintaining the privacy of your information is a top priority as we go about our business. For that reason, we have established practices and procedures for handling information at JustFly that we believe follow the highest standards and best practices of organisations doing business on the Internet, and that also comply with applicable laws and regulations.

We have spelled out our privacy policy (the “Policy”) here on our website for you to read. It details the practices we employ in the operation of this website with respect to the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information.

An informed consumer is an empowered consumer. And we believe you should be fully informed about our information-handling procedures so you can properly decide for yourself whether to use this website and, if so, to what extent. That’s why we’ve taken the time to prepare a detailed privacy policy … to empower you.

Simply stated:

  * JustFly will not collect personally-identifiable information like your name, e-mail and mailing addresses and telephone numbers (“Personal Information”) without your prior knowledge and permission;
  * JustFly will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties unless you give us permission to do so, or unless required to do so by law;
  * JustFly will allow you to view, change or remove your Personal Information and other information associated with your registration as a user of our website; and
  * JustFly will take reasonable steps to protect the security and confidentiality of the Personal Information we collect from you.

**Perusing Our Website Content**

You can visit and browse our website without revealing your identity or disclosing any Personal Information.

We do automatically collect usage information when people visit our website. However, this information is anonymous data that is not linked to those visitors personally. We use this data to better understand, for example, how visitors navigate our website, how many visitors arrive at what pages on the website, the frequency of visits to the website and how long visitors stay, and the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses from which visitors come to our website.

This type of usage information is regularly collected by Internet server software for most websites and is a common practice. And again, the information collected is anonymous.

JustFly uses this data to improve the website’s content, performance and usability so as to provide you with a better experience on future visits to the website.

**Cookies and Pixel Tagging**

When you visit our website, or a website on which we advertise, our computers (as well as those of third-party advertisers we link to) may attempt to place a “cookie” or a “pixel tag” on the computer you are using to access these websites.

Cookies and pixel tags are small computer files (i.e., computer software) that a website saves to your computer by way of your web browser. Your computer then sends that software back to the originating website every time you make a request on that website.

This software makes the personalization of your Internet usage possible. It collects data on your usage of a website that then helps us personalize and improve your online experience. Please note that data on your use of a website may be linked to the Personal Information you supply when you register on that website.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser to either stop accepting cookies altogether or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the websites you visit.

Please be aware that if you opt not to accept cookies or similar software from our website, you may not be able to use some of the features on our website, or your use of them may be impaired.

To learn more about the use of cookies, pixel tags and similar software, the information-gathering practices of our network-advertising partners and about opting out of accepting cookies, please visit http://networkadvertising.org.

**Third-party Advertisers**

JustFly may at any point, and without notice, host third-party advertisers on this website. “Third-party advertisers” refers to marketing companies that advertise on the Internet. These advertisers may use cookies, pixel tags and/or similar software to gather information about the ads you view online, your browsing history and the subjects you seem to be interested in. These advertisers may use the information about your visits to our website as well as other websites to then present you with ads for products and services you may be interested in.

JustFly does not and will not share any of your Personal Information with these advertisers unless you give us specific permission to do so. This permission is separate from any permission you give us when you register on this website.

This privacy policy does not extend to or cover the practices of these third-party advertisers.

We offer personalized shopping experiences and advertising through Intent Media, which uses online identifiers to identify visitors. To view Intent Media’s privacy policy, click [here](http://intentmedia.com/privacy-policy/). To opt out, click [here](http://www.intentmedia.com/opt-out).

**Personal Information**

When you register with us on our website, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily provide to us. This Personal Information is necessary for us to be able to provide you with the products and services offered on our website, and includes such information as your name, address, email address and telephone numbers.

**Traveller Profile**

JustFly creates a “Traveller Profile” on you when you register on our website. Your Traveller Profile contains your Personal Information plus whatever other information you willingly share with us. We also add to your Traveller Profile data we collect about how you use our website. And we may also include information about you that we obtain from outside sources, for example e-tickets or itineraries from airlines you’ve used.

We gather and use all this information to help us maximize our overall service to you and to provide you the best possible user experience. For example, we may use the information in your Traveller Profile to personalize the service we provide you; to communicate with you about your travel plans and about new features and special offers; and to better align various features of our website to optimize your use of the website.

**Opt-out**

When you register on this website, you are given the option to either receive or opt out of receiving updates, promotions and advertisements by email.

More specifically, we offer two types of emails: (1) our monthly newsletter, which brings you useful tips and information related to travel as well as flight specials, contests and other unique travel opportunities available on our website or through our travel partners; and (2) update emails featuring the latest flight specials, promotions and other unique travel opportunities available on our website or through our travel partners and advertisers. Please let us know which, if any, of these emails you would like to receive.

We encourage you to receive these emails to enhance your experience with us and to help us better meet your vacation and travel needs. If you do opt to receive these emails, we will use the information you provide us about your travel interests and preferences to send you customized promotions and updates that include our recommended travel specials.

We use a variety of methods to send these emails, including an e-mail delivery and marketing company. Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those e-mail messages as well as at our website to help us learn how visitors are using our website and to measure the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication, or by contacting us at the following address: [justfly@justflyemail.com](mailto:justfly@justflyemail.com)

**Online Surveys and Contests**

In our on-going effort to improve our service, we value user comments and feedback. We may periodically invite you, as a registered user of this website, to participate in online surveys. Participation is optional, and the choice of whether to participate is yours. In addition, whenever you purchase or reserve travel-related products or services through this website, your Travel Consultant may ask for feedback on your experience.

Your participation in these surveys is anonymous unless we tell you otherwise upfront.

From time to time, we sponsor contests, offering you a chance to win travel-related prizes. Sometimes, participation in these contests involves completing an online survey. It is always your choice whether or not to participate in these contests.

If you do choose to participate in one or more of our contests, you must provide us with certain Personal Information, such as your full name, mailing address and email address. We will only use this Personal Information to notify you if you win a contest.

**Payment Information and Travel History**

Registering with us on this website allows you to book, reserve and purchase travel-related products, services and accommodations on and through the website. To register, in addition to your Personal Information, you must also provide us with payment information, such as your credit card number, expiration date, cardholder name and your billing address. We will add this information to your Traveller Profile, discussed above in this Policy (Traveller Profile).

We will maintain a record of all your bookings, reservations and purchases of travel-related products, services and accommodations in your Traveller Profile, unless you opt to edit your Traveller Profile otherwise as described below in this Policy (Changing/Removing Personal Information or Other Information).

**Itinerary Changes & Travel Alerts**

When you book, reserve or purchase travel-related products or services through our website, you will be given the option to receive, or have others receive, updates and alerts about your travel arrangements, such as changes in airport gate assignments or delays in departures or arrivals. We call this a “Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert.”

A Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert can be sent to you or to anyone else you designate by telephone, email, text message, pager or other wireless device.

A Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert can be sent to you or to anyone else you designate by telephone, email, text message, pager or other wireless device.

If you opt to have a Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert sent to someone other than you, we will need to collect Personal Information about that person necessary to send a Travel Itinerary & Travel Alert to that person, such as the person’s name, phone number and/or email address. Of course, you will need to obtain that other person’s prior consent to disclose their Personal Information for this purpose.

In the ordinary course of our business, we only share your Personal Information with those travel providers whom you make travel arrangements with through our website. For example, if you purchase an airline ticket, reserve a rental car or book a hotel room on our website, we will provide that airline, rental car company or hotel with the Personal Information needed to process your order.

We take reasonable care to ensure that these travel providers will protect your Personal Information as much as we do. We take the security of your Personal Information very seriously, and we insist that they do too.

Similarly, we hire and work with various outside companies to perform some of the functions needed to operate our business, such as processing credit cards, delivering tickets and shipping items. Just as with travel providers mentioned above, we share with these outside companies only that Personal Information needed to process your order. And these companies have agreed not to use or disclose that Personal Information for any other purpose.

Other than as explained elsewhere in this Policy, we will not disclose any Personal Information we collect from you to others without your prior permission, except in certain limited and unusual circumstances: (a) to protect the security of our website and our rights under our Terms and Conditions of Use; (b) to protect ourselves against liability; (c) in response to legal process or judicial order; (d) if we believe in good faith that the law requires it; (e) in connection with the sale of our business or company; or (f) as required by government security regulations.

We will notify you if any when any such disclosure is made.

In making travel arrangements, you are welcome to request special foods or meals either based on religious beliefs or dietary restrictions. However, please be aware that in doing so, certain religious and/or health information may be deduced about you by the travel provider receiving your request. Therefore, when you request special foods or meals, your permission is deemed granted to forward this request to the travel provider knowing this may reveal personal religious and/or health information about you.

Also, travelers to or from the United States may have their Personal Information captured by the U.S. Department of Homeland Security, which may store it for up to 50 years. Further, this information can be shared with other agencies and departments of the U.S. Government.

**Corporate Travel**

You may purchase travel services or accommodations for corporate travel purposes through our website. You must tell us during the purchase process that the purchase is for corporate travel purposes. You can do this by either specifying in the booking path that the purchase is for corporate travel or specifying that the credit card you are using is a corporate credit card.

We will provide your corporation with as much of your Personal Information as is necessary for it to track the corporate travel you’ve purchased through our website if (1) you or someone acting on your behalf do purchase travel services or accommodations through our website, (2) you or someone acting on your behalf tells us that the purchase is for corporate travel purposes as described above, and (3) we have an agreement in place with your corporation to provide it with data on the purchases of travel services or accommodations by its employees.

Other Travellers 

You may book, reserve or purchase travel services or accommodations for other people using your Traveller Profile. If you do, we will collect certain Personal Information about these other people, and we will retain these other people’s Personal Information in your Traveller Profile.

Please be sure to obtain each such person’s prior consent to disclose their Personal Information to us for this purpose.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our website contains links to other websites on the Internet. When you click on one of these links, your web browser leaves our website and opens up the website to which that link connects. We have no control over that linked website and are not responsible for its contents, links or functions.

Since we work with outside companies to provide some of the services we offer on our website (e.g., to purchase travel insurance), our website may automatically link you directly to that outside company’s website, where you may be asked to provide Personal Information. Our privacy policy does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by these outside companies.

We recommend that you thoroughly read the privacy policy or statement of any website you visit through a link on our website. That website’s privacy policy or statement governs your visit to and use of that website, and may be very different from our privacy policy. This is especially the case if you decide to register with that website or purchase any products or services on that website.

**Changing/Removing Personal Information or Other Information**

We appreciate the trust you place in us when you give us your Personal Information as well as other information. We value that trust and want to continue to deserve it. Therefore, we allow you to have as much control over the Personal Information and other information we have about you as possible.

By contacting your Travel Consultant, you can do the following:

  * change the password for your account;
  * view the Personal Information and other information in your Traveller Profile;
  * change the preferences associated with your account;
  * change, correct or update the Personal Information and other information in your Traveller Profile; and
  * remove some or all of the Personal Information and other information in your Traveller Profile.

Should you request that we remove all of the Personal Information and other information in your Traveler Profile, we will promptly do so. However, please be aware that if you do so, you will not be able to use our services unless you register anew.

You may also request to have all of your travel records removed from our system. We will then do so within seven (7) months after receiving your request. This seven-month timeframe is necessary to ensure that travel arrangements made through our website are properly accounted for and to allow for the redundancy of our data backup system.

You will not have the ability to view, change or remove from your Traveller Profile session data and/or information we have gathered from third parties. To do this, you must make the necessary arrangements with those third parties.

We may not be able to honour your request to remove your Personal Information or travel records if we are legally obligated to retain that information or records. For example, some records, such as taxation and other financial records, are legally required to be retained for up to 7 years, and we are obligated to comply.

**Notification of Changes**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time.

If we make any material changes to the Policy (e.g., a change regarding disclosure of Personal Information), we will either (a) post notice of the change(s) on our website, (b) display notice of the change(s) on a pop-up screen on our website, and/or (c) notify you of the change(s) via email to the email address you gave us. Whichever method(s) we choose to employ, we will do so at least thirty (30) days before the change takes effect.

On the other hand, if we make any less significant changes to the Policy, we will simply post notice of the change(s) on our website, and we will do so at least thirty (30) days before the change takes effect.

If you do not agree with any of our intended changes and are not willing to accept that change(s), you may, as discussed in the preceding section (Changing/Removing Personal Information or Other Information), request that we remove your Personal Information and/or other information from our records.

**Combined Non-Personal Information**

We may combine anonymous information you and other users of this website provide to us when you register on the website with data about how you and others use our website. We may then use this combined information to describe our user base to potential partners, investors, advertisers and others. This information is presented without reference to any specific user, and no Personal Information is disclosed.

We may use information we collect about your travel preferences and experiences to make travel recommendations to other users of this website (without sharing or disclosing any of your Personal Information). For example, if we know from our collected information that you and other users of this website had a good experience at a particular hotel in a particular city, we may then recommend that hotel to other users of this website who will be travelling to that same city.

We may share aggregated statistical data about users of our website and purchasers of certain products and services on our website with our vendors, partners and other outside companies. This statistical information is never linked to any Personal Information that can identify you personally.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We are absolutely committed to safeguarding your information and keeping it secure. To help us do so, we employ security technology professionals and have deployed a full range of leading-edge security technology. Specifically, your information is secured from unauthorised access via the Internet through leading firewall technology, Virtual Private Networks and alarm systems.

In addition, we or our associates protect the connection between your computer and our server from eavesdropping through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 128 bits.

We continually evaluate new technologies and strategies for protecting confidential information to ensure that our information-handling practices remain in accordance with the highest standards in the industry and best practices on the Internet at all times. This helps us keep our commitment to you to maintain the privacy and integrity of your information.

**Children and Minors**

Children and minors (individuals under 18 years of age) are ineligible and not allowed to register on our website or use the services available on and through the website.

Many JustFly staff members are parents. JustFly believes parents should play a central role in their children’s online activities and should monitor those activities to ensure that any websites visited respect the privacy of children and minors.

**Contact Us**

We have set forth our privacy policy as thoroughly as possible to address your legitimate concerns about protecting your Personal Information. Should you have any questions, concerns or suggestions regarding this Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us by email at support@JustFly.com. We will make our best effort to respond to your questions or comments within five (5) business days after we receive them. Thank you.
